{
    "id": "3d1555fe6c3245adaa8b661b29f2b088",
    "title": "Perfect Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We …………….. in this house for the past three years .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have stayed",
                "have been staying",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The students …………….. on an educational tour.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have gone",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Only those students who ………………… ‘A’ grades will be considered for admission.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are securing",
                "have secured",
                "have been securing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Sorry I am late. ………………….. you ……………….. long?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Are, waiting",
                "Have, waited",
                "Have, been waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ………………… that book, you should return it to the library.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have read",
                "are reading",
                "have been reading"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Sorry about the mess – I …………………. the walls.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am painting",
                "have painted",
                "have been painting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………. ten candies since lunchtime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are eating",
                "have been eating",
                "have eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… six letters since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am writing",
                "have written",
                "have been writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. a lot of films recently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "am watching",
                "have been watching"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. three films this week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "have watched",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}